http://www.sustainableharvest.org/privacy-policy

Donate
Privacy PolicyOUR COMMITMENT TO DONOR PRIVACYWhen you donate to Sustainable Harvest International (SHI), we are committed to protecting the privacy of our donors. We treat all of our donors’ personal information as confidential. That means that we absolutely do not sell, rent, give-away or share any of our donors’ personal information. Further, we do not send donor mailings on behalf of any other organization.USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONWhen you donate to SHI, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. When you browse our website, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system. With your permission, we may send you emails about our organization and other updates.If you have registered to receive email communications from us and later change your mind, you may contact us to have your name removed from our distribution lists. You have the following options to do this: by email hello@sustainableharvest.org, by phone: 207-669-8254 or by mail:Sustainable Harvest International177 Huntington Ave Ste 1703 #23701Boston, Massachusetts 02115CONSENTWhen you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, or other services, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only. If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no. DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIESIn the unlikely event of a request for personal information by a law enforcement agency, we may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.THIRD-PARTY SERVICESWe use third parties to provide certain services on our website. For such services, we may share your personal information with these third-party providers only to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. Because we care about the privacy of your information, we use only highly-reputable third-party service providers. These third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have implemented their own measures to keep your information secure. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which they will handle your personal information. In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.SECURITYTo protect your personal information, we follow industry best practices to make sure it is not lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. If you provide us with your credit card information, that information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.  Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.AGE OF CONSENTBy using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on our website. We will not materially alter the use of our personal information without contacting you directly and requesting your consent.QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, email hello@sustainableharvest.org, call 207-669-8254, or send us a letter:Sustainable Harvest International177 Huntington Ave Ste 1703 #23701Boston, Massachusetts 02115
Press + AwardsRequest a SpeakerStaff (Internal)Board (Internal)Financial ArchivePartnershipsState Disclosure InformationContactF.A.QSign UpPrivacy Policy
